dancehallhiphop.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy - Urban Islandz

## Privacy Statement

#### 1\. Purpose

Urban Islandz has adopted this Privacy Statement in order to inform you of its policies with respect to information collected from this website. Your use of this website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Statement and your consent to the practices it describes.

#### 2\. Automatic Collection of Anonymous Information

When you visit Urban Islandz website, like when you visit most other websites, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged, which may include information about the type of browser you use, the server name and IP address through which you access the internet (such as “aol.com” or “earthlink.net”), the date and time you access the site, the pages you access while at Urban Islandz’s website, and the internet address of the website, if any, from which you linked directly to Urban Islandz’s site. This information is not personally identifiable.

#### 3\. Personally Identifiable Information

Personally Identifiable Information is any information that concerns you individually and would permit someone to contact you, for example, your name, address, telephone number, email address or any information you submitted to urbanislandz.com that identifies you individually.

Urban Islandz.com will not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you provide it. Therefore, if you do not want urbanislandz.com to obtain any personally identifiable information about you, do not submit it.

You can visit and browse Urban Islandz’s website without revealing personally identifiable information about yourself. You may also choose to disclose personally identifiable information about yourself, which may be maintained as described below. Urban Islandz.com may collect personally identifiable information about you from its website by methods such as the following:

#### 4\. Registration Forms

If you are offered the opportunity to enter a promotion or to become a registered user of Urban Islandz’s website, you must apply by filling out the registration form on the site. This form requires certain personally identifiable information that may include, without limitation, your name, email address, postal address, telephone number and/or a unique individual password.

#### 5\. Transactions and Activity

If you become a registered user or if you conduct transactions through Urban Islandz’s website, it collects information about the transactions you engage in while on the website and your other activity on the site. This information may include, without limitation, areas of the website that you visit, transaction type, content that you view, download or submit, transaction amount and payment information.

#### 6\. Email and other voluntary communications

You may also choose to communicate with Urban Islandz through email, via our website, by telephone, in writing, or through other means. We collect the information in these communications, and such information may be personally identifiable.

#### 7\. Information Use

Urban Islandz may use the personally identifiable information collected through its website primarily for such purposes as:  
a) helping to establish and verify the identity of users;  
b) opening, maintaining, administering and servicing users’ accounts or memberships;  
c) processing, servicing or enforcing transactions and sending related communications;  
d) providing services and support to users;  
e) improving the website, including tailoring it to users’ preferences;  
f) providing users with service updates, promotional notices and offers, and other information about Urban Islandz;  
g) responding to your questions inquiries, comments and instructions;  
h) maintaining the security and integrity of its systems.

Urban Islandz uses the anonymous browsing information collected automatically by its servers primarily to help it administer and improve its website. Urban Islandz.com may also use aggregated anonymous information to provide information about its website to potential business partners and other unaffiliated entities. Again, this information is not personally identifiable.

#### 8\. Disclosure of Information

Urban Islandz does not provide personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their use in marketing directly to you. Urban Islandz may use unaffiliated companies to help it maintain and operate its website or for other reasons related to the operation of its business, and those companies may receive your personally identifiable information for that purpose. Urban Islandz may also disclose personally identifiable information about you in connection with legal requirements, such as in response to an authorized subpoena, governmental request or investigation, or as otherwise permitted by law. Finally, as Urban Islandz’s business develops, it may sell or buy corporate assets, and in such transactions customer information may be one of the transferred business assets. If Urban Islandz, its internet businesses, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired, customer information may be one of the assets transferred.

#### 9\. “Cookies” and Advertisers

Urban Islandz website’s server, or the servers of companies that are used to operate this site, may place a “cookie” on your computer in order to allow you to use the website and to personalize your experience.

A “cookie” is a small piece of data that can be sent by a web server to your computer, which then may be stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow urbanislandz.com to recognize your computer while you are on its website and help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you. Cookies are also useful in allowing more efficient log-in for users, tracking transaction histories and preserving information between sessions. The information collected from cookies may also be used to improve the functionality of the website.

The advertisers and/or other content providers that may appear on this website may also use cookies that are not sent by Urban Islandz’s website. Such ads or content may contain cookies that help track and target the interests of users of this website in order to present “personalized” advertisements or other messages that the user might find interesting. Urban Islandz is not responsible for any such cookies.

Most web browser applications (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer) have features that can notify you when you receive a cookie or prevent cookies from being sent. If you disable cookies, however, you may not be able to use certain personalized functions of this website.

#### 10\. Security

Urban Islandz maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard personally identifiable information. If transactions are offered on the site, transaction information is transmitted to and from urbanislandz.com in encrypted form using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception. Urban Islandz restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. Please be aware, however, that any email or other transmission you send through the internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.

#### 11\. Infinite Scroll

Data Used: In order to record page views via WordPress.com Stats (which must be enabled for page view tracking here to work) with additional loads, the following information is used: IP address, WordPress.com user ID (if logged in), WordPress.com username (if logged in), user agent, visiting URL, referring URL, timestamp of event, browser language, country code.

Activity Tracked: Page views will be tracked with each additional load (i.e. when you scroll down to the bottom of the page and a new set of posts loads automatically). If the site owner has enabled Google Analytics to work with this feature, a page view event will also be sent to the appropriate Google Analytics account with each additional load.

#### 12\. Sharing

Data Used: When sharing content via email (this option is only available if Akismet is active on the site), the following information is used: sharing party’s name and email address (if the user is logged in, this information will be pulled directly from their account), IP address (for spam checking), user agent (for spam checking), and email body/content. This content will be sent to Akismet (also owned by Automattic) so that a spam check can be performed. Additionally, if reCAPTCHA (by Google) is enabled by the site owner, the sharing party’s IP address will be shared with that service. You can find Google’s privacy policy here.

#### 13\. Subscriptions

Data Used: To initiate and process subscriptions, the following information is used: subscriber’s email address and the ID of the post or comment (depending on the specific subscription being processed). In the event of a new subscription being initiated, we also collect some basic server data, including all of the subscribing user’s HTTP request headers, the IP address from which the subscribing user is viewing the page, and the URI which was given in order to access the page (REQUEST_URI and DOCUMENT_URI). This server data used for the exclusive purpose of monitoring and preventing abuse and spam.

Activity Tracked: Functionality cookies are set for a duration of 347 days to remember a visitor’s blog and post subscription choices if, in fact, they have an active subscription.

#### 14\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Urban Islandz reserves the right to modify or supplement this policy at any time. If a material change to the terms of this policy is made, Urban Islandz will post a link to the new policy on its website.

#### 15\. Contacting Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement or the information practices of Urban Islandz, please contact us by email [here](https://urbanislandz.com/about-2/contact-us/).
